## **Thomas** FEVRE

## FULLSTACK DEVELOPER & BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

### **EXPERIENCE**

# FULL STACK & BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER METADEV3

Sep 2022 - Present

Develop web2 & web3 Frontend and Backend solutions, both on web and mobile platforms.

Design and develop smart contract architectures.

Conduct blockchain protocol technology watch.

Perform integration and unit testing.

### **MAIN PROJECTS AT METADEV3:**

# BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER CODENEKT

May 2024 - July 2024

Design and develop smart contract architectures (using Diamond pattern).

Integrate web3 into web2 production API servers.

Perform smart-contracts unit testing.

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER QWEEZAP

Nov 2023 - Jan 2024

Develop backend APIs and mobile & web applications (Flutter). Implement ERC-20 token and integrate multiple NFT collections. Integrate Aws.

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER E-SOVREIGNTY

Jan 2023 - Oct 2023

Develop web3 DApp & mobile version using Flutter (meta-transactions with OpenZeppelin Defender).

Contribute to cryptographic solution R&D.

Develop smart contracts and implement unit tests (using Diamond pattern).

# BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER BOLLERO MUSIC

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

Develop DEX smart contracts for token and liquidity pool management.

Research and compare market-making protocols.

Implement DEX functionalities and deploy.

#### CONTACT

Thomas.fevre@outlook.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/thomas-fevre-6853b51a1

#### **ABOUT ME**

https://github.com/thomasfevre https://github.com/tfevre

Passionate Full Stack Developer with many years of experience, specializing in Blockchain technology. Quick adaptation, perseverance, and curiosity. Thrives on technical challenges and knowledge sharing. Key player in web, mobile and blockchain project architectures.

### **SKILLS**

### Languages

Solidity, TypeScript/JavaScript, Dart, Python, Php, HTML, CSS

#### **Frameworks**

Flutter, Tailwind, Flask, jQuery, Laravel, NestJS, Quasar, ReactJS, NextJS, VueJS, AngularJS

#### Blockchain

EVM-Compatible & Solana

#### **Tools**

Git, AWS, Hardhat, Foundry, Web3Auth, Cometh, Pinata, OpenZeppelin Defender, QuickNode, Tenderly, Redis, Firebase

#### **Databases**

PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB

### **Standards**

ERC20, ERC721, ERC1155, EIP2535, EIP4337, EIP2771

### **EDUCATION**

## ESILV 2022 - 2024 (École Supérieure d'Ingénieurs Léonardde-Vinci)

Engineering degree in Full Stack Development, specializing in Blockchain and Fintech

### CESI École d'Ingénieur 2019 - 2022

Preparatory classes and first year of Computer Engineering